http://www.joylight.com/terms.html

Joy Light Center
Home
Services
Psychic Medium or Psychic. What is the difference.
Terms
JOY LIGHT CENTER, TERMS OF USE/DISCLAIMERUse of this website is of your own free will and constitutes acceptance of this and all other terms of our privacy statement, disclaimer, policies and terms of use as follows:By scheduling and purchasing of any service offered and/or paying for any services offered you are stating that you have read this legal disclaimer of service and that you understand and willingly enter into, agree with, and accept the following:READINGS AND ADVICEAll reading sessions and advice arising from use of this site are understood to be for entertainment purposes only and are for persons 18 years old or older. Insights, guidance and awareness provided is intended to help clients with life choices, however, a client is always free to make their own choices based on free will and such choices or actions are their sole responsibility. Interpretation of information presented in a session is not meant to replace medical, legal, psychological or other professional advice or services. All psychic readings and consultations are meant for entertainment purposes only and in no way constitute legal, financial or professional advice for which professional licensure is required. Psychic advice and consultations do not constitute diagnosis or treatment of any illness, be it mental, physical, or spiritual. Discussion pertaining to medical or legal matters is for general information purposes only. Any advice provided does not constitute medical or legal advice which should be sought from a qualified medical or legal professional.By engaging in any reading session with an adviser or owner of joylight.com you agree such person shall not be liable for action or non-action taken by client in reference to the information conveyed during the session and understand that adviser or owner of joylight.com makes no representations or warranties, express or implied, with respect to the accuracy, relevancy, or quality of information and do not assume and hereby disclaim any liability to any person or entity for any loss or damages (including, without limitation, physical, mental, special, indirect, incidental or consequential) caused in regard to any information and or suggestions(s) or advice provided, regardless of whether resulting from negligence, accident, or any other cause whatsoever.LIABILITY DISCLAIMERJoy Light Center. joylight.com makes no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, as to the operation of the site, the information, content, materials or products included on this site, nor does inclusion in this site constitute an endorsement of any product or service listed. You agree Joy Light Center, owner joylight.com and psychic adviser will not be liable for any damages arising from use of this site and agree to completely hold blameless and absolutely indemnify such person from any and all liabilities and expenses. All reading sessions and advice arising from use of this site are understood to be for entertainment purposes only and are for persons age 18 or older. Links to websites outside of Joy Light Center are owned and operated independent of Joy Light Center, joylight.com and their information, content, materials, products, policies, terms, representations, or warranties, express or implied, is not under the control of or the responsibility of Joy Light Center.PAYMENT INFORMATIONJoy Light Center, joylight.com and associated jlcshops.com, accepts payment through the SECURE third party credit card system, PayPal.com. We will never have access to your credit card information, as PayPal keeps that information secure and private for you. We will have access to your order content, shipping address, email address, but only for the purpose of processing your order or contacting you if necessary. If you do not have a PayPal account, you can set one up in a few minutes on any order page or use the credit card option. Links from the Joy Light Center Site to other websites is independent of Joy Light Center and they have their own payment processing system. If you have any questions about obtaining a service provided by a website other than Joy Light Center, you should read that websites policy for details.PRIVACY STATEMENT FOR JOY LIGHT CENTERJoy Light Center has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: Joy Light CenterInformation Automatically Logged We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information.Cookies Our Site uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. Cookies used by our affiliate networks or websites linked from Joy Light Center are under the control of those networks and are used to keep track of your shopping cart. Cookies of the affiliate sites may be used to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit their site. The Joy Light Center does not have access to this private information, nor do we share information with our affiliate network. We do however, have access to broad demographic statistical information such as view impressions and click thru information that tracks users of the affiliate sites.Advertisers We may at times use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by the ad company, and we do not have access to this information.Forms Our site's forms requires users to give us contact information (like their name, email, and postal address), and demographic information (like their zip code).Contact information from the forms is used to respond to inquiries for information. The customer's contact information may also be used to get in touch with the customer when necessary.Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.External Links This site contains links to other sites. Joy Light Center is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.Special Relationships We have a network of special relationships, such as content providers, business associates, co-branded sites, affiliate network referral systems. We do not own the information supplied by these special relationships, we do not control who is receiving the information collected by the site and who has access to this information. Only select information is shared for the purpose of conducting business, such as statistical information or information gathered to produce charts and reports or provide services. This information is limited to only aggregate information for the purpose of computing commissions or to fill order requests.Security This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. These measures only include being able to make changes to form data or web content under the control of the Joy Light Center.Children's Guidelines We care about children and understand that they have special privacy needs. Therefore, we have adopted the following privacy policy regarding children:We will NOT knowingly collect, use, or distribute to third parties personally identifiable information.We will NOT knowingly give the child access to unmonitored chat rooms, message boards, email accounts, or other services under our conrol that would give the child the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable information.If we become aware that a minor has requested information, we may opt to use the online contact information (such as email) to: Respond directly to the child's request on a one-time basis and not use that information to re-contact the child for other purposes. Request the name or online contact information of a parent for the purpose of obtaining verifiable parental consent or providing parental notification. Respond more than once directly to a specific request from a child (such as in the case where a child requests a newsletter subscription) and not used to re-contact the child for other purposes. We will use our best efforts to provide parental notification, which will include the nature and intended use as well as an opportunity for the parent to prevent the use of the information and participation in the activity. We will NOT entice the child to divulge more information than is needed to provide parential notification. We will provide the parent a description of the specific types of a personally identifiable information collected from their child upon request. We will allow for a parent to obtain any personally identifiable information collected from their child. We will provide notice to children in age appropriate terms of what personally identifiable information is to be collected. We will NOT provide any printed astrology or numerology reports or charts to children. We do not knowingly provide psychic readings to minors. We will encourage children to get their parent's permission before sharing personal information online. For services on this site under our control relating to psychic readings the recepient be 18 years of age or older. Contacting the Web Site If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: Joy Light Center via our contact formLEGAL NOTICESCopywrite and Trademark InformationJoy Light Center, Joy Light Center logo and derivatives, Joy Light Center Shops logo, Happy logo, All About You Numerology Reports, Compatibility Chart, Joy Light graphics, pictures, photos, in any format displayed on this site, joylight.com and jlcshops.com, are all copyright and/or trademarks of Joy Light Center. These may be used publicly with written permission only from joylight.com, owner, Joy Light Center. Fair use of Joy Light Center, joylight.com trademarks in advertising and promotion of joylight.com products requires proper acknowledgement. All other brands and names are property of their respective owners.Warranties and Limitation of Liability, Site Content, Legal Disclaimer, Personal Use, Commercial Use, Licensed Logo UseThe information contained herein is provided to the Joy Light Center by various parties. While the Joy Light Center makes every effort to present accurate and reliable information on this Internet site, the Joy Light Center, joylight.com, does not endorse, approve or certify such information, nor does it guarantee the accuracy, completeness, efficacy, timeliness, or correct sequencing of such information. Use of such information is voluntary, and reliance on it should only be undertaken after an independent review of its accuracy, completeness, efficacy, and timeliness. Reference herein to any specific commercial product, process, or service by trade name, trademark, service mark, manufacturer, or otherwise does not necessarily constitute or imply endorsement, recommendation, or favoring by the Joy Light Center. No information or service provided on this site is intended to replace the advise of professionals for which professional liscensure is required.The Joy Light Center assumes no responsibility for consequences resulting from the use of the information herein, (or for the use of the information obtained at linked Internet addresses), or in any respect for the content of such information, including (but not limited to) errors or omissions, the accuracy or reasonableness of factual or scientific assumptions, studies or conclusions, the defamatory nature of statements, ownership of copyright or other intelletual property rights, and the violation of property, privacy or personal rights of others. The Joy Light Center is not responsible for, and expressly disclaims all liability for, damages of any kind arising out of use, reference to, or reliance on such information. No guarantees or warranties, including (but not limited to) any express or implied warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular use or purpose, are made by the Joy Light Center with respect to such information.This site contains links to other sites. The Joy Light Center is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Websites. We are, however, participant in affiliate, associate, and co-branded sites. We make every effort to screen these programs for appropriate content and purpose prior to participation, but are not responsible for consequences resulting from the use of these sites not under our control. Information and documents provided on this web site are provided "as is" without warranty. Your use of this web site is at your own risk.joylight.com hereby authorizes you to view, copy, download, and print joylight.com documents that are available and under the control of joylight.com website, subject to the following conditions:The documents may be used solely for personal, noncommercial, and informational purposes. The documents may not be modified. The following copyright notice and permission notice must appear in each document: "Copyright (c), Joy Light Center. All Rights Reserved. Protected by the copyright laws of the United States and international treaties". Copyright, trademark, and other proprietary notices may not be removed.You may not reproduce, copy, or redistribute the design or layout of the joylight.com web site, individual elements of the web site design, or joylight.com logos, images, pictures without express written permission.Reproduction, copying, or redistribution for commercial purposes of any materials or design elements on the joylight.com web site is strictly prohibited without express written permission.Use, reproduction, copying or redistribution of joylight.com logos is strictly prohibited without express written permission.DisclaimerAll services provided by joylight.com may be used for lawful purposes only. We do not provide any services to sites containing material in violation of any Federal, State or City law. The user agrees to indemnify and hold harmless Joy Light Center and or owner joylight.com, jlcshops.com from and against any and all liability, claims, losses, damages, injuries, or expenses (including) reasonable attorney fees) resulting from the use of the service which damages the user or any other parties.
Joy Light Center, 4933 W 600 N, Fairland, IN 46126, copyright 1996 - 2020, All Rights Reserved. Terms of Use, Disclaimer.                                                                               Site powered by Weebly. Managed by Verio
Home
Services
Psychic Medium or Psychic. What is the difference.
